Billy Byers Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Full Scores (Box 1-35)
  - Rodgers/Hart tv special, 1976
    - Family of man medley, Includes: "Soliloquy;" "One foot, other foot;" "You’ve got to be carefully taught;" "An ordinary couple;" "When the children are asleep;" "Hello young lovers;" "You’ll never walk alone."; For Sammy Davis, Jr./Diahann Carroll. (Box-folder 26/13)
  - Rogers, Ginger
    - Forty second Street: nightclub, 1978 (Box-folder 26/14)
    - Hooray for Hollywood: nightclub, 1978 (Box-folder 26/15)
    - Night and day: nightclub, 1978 (Box-folder 26/16)
  - Ross, Diana see also The Supremes (Motown girls)
    - Fine and mellow: pre-score production #10474/M-117/M-116, Photocopies taped together; probably from film Lady Day; arrangement may be by Mike Barone. (Box-folder 26/17)
    - Good morning heartache: production #10474 pre score/M-113, Photocopies taped together; probably from film Lady Day; arrangement may be by Mike Barone. (Box-folder 26/18)
    - Rodgers and Hart medley: Motown vaudeville arrangement, Feb. 5, 1971, Includes "Little girl blue;" "My funny Valentine;" "Thou swell;" "Mountain greenery." (Box-folder 26/19)
    - September of my years: Motown production/tv/Gil Askey (Box-folder 26/20)
    - What did I have: Motown vaudeville arrangement, Feb. 5, 1971 (Box-folder 26/21)
  - Rowles, Stacey
    - I fall in love too easily: Sept 12. 1973 (Box-folder 26/22)
  - Rubins, Paula
    - Bossa chant (Box-folder 26/23)
    - Merry-go-round (Box-folder 26/24)
    - Quest (Box-folder 26/25)
  - Run America live tv, 1978
    - Animation (m1) (Box-folder 27/1)
    - Details (Box-folder 27/2)
    - Foot ballet (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Gizzoutas (Box-folder 27/4)
    - The greatest love of all, For Tom Sullivan. (Box-folder 27/5)
    - Main title (m2) (Box-folder 27/6)
    - My way, For Gaillard. (Box-folder 27/7)
    - Nobody does it better, For Tom Sullivan. (Box-folder 27/8)
    - Pyramid montage (Box-folder 27/9)
    - Running boog (Box-folder 27/10)
    - Running shuffle (Box-folder 27/11)
    - Running theme (Box-folder 27/12)
    - Salute to the Olympians - (Mancini) (Box-folder 27/13)
  - Scott & David
    - 60's medley, Includes "Sergeant Pepper’s Lonely Heart’s Club Band;" "Day tripper." (Box-folder 27/14)
  - Severinsen, Doc see also Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
    - Severinsen/Armstrong suite, Includes "Mack the Knife;" "Hello Dolly;" "When the saints go marching in." (Box-folder 27/15)
  - Shangri La bows, Arranged by Nan Schwartz. (Box-folder 27/16)
  - Sherman, Bobby see The Music Scene
  - Sinatra, Frank see also Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
    - A foggy day: April 15, 1970, Includes printed copy. (Box-folder 27/17)
  - Sinatra, Frank Jr. see also Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
    - I’ll never smile again (Box-folder 27/18)
  - Sinatra, Nancy see also Lambert, Hugh and Nancy Sinatra
    - Blondes: Feb. 2, 1972 (Box-folder 27/19)
    - I’m flying: Aug. 8, 1971 (Box-folder 27/20)
    - I’m not afraid: May 21, 1971 (Box-folder 27/21)
    - Personality (Box-folder 27/22)
    - Places medley: May 8, 1973, Includes "Sentimental journey;" "San Francisco;" "Galveston;" "Wichita lineman;" "Indiana;" "Homeward bound;" "Kansas City;" "Abilene;" "Jackson;" "I want to go back to Michigan;" "Alabamy bound;" "Chicago;" "Do you know what it means to miss New Orleans;" "Dear hearts and gentle people;" "Doin’ what comes natur’lly;" "Don’t fence me in;" "I’m an old cowhand;" "She’ll be comin’ round the mountain;" "On top of old Smokey;: "On Broadway;" "Lullaby of Broadway."; For Nancy Sinatra, the Everly Brothers and others. (Box-folder 27/23)
    - Rain and sun medley: 1973, Includes "Rainy days and Mondays;" "Here’s that rainy day;" "Stormy weather;" "When the sun comes out." (Box-folder 27/24)
  - Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
    - Nancy and Frank Jr. medley, Includes "Nancy with the laughin’ face;" "Mighty lak’ a rose;" "I’ll never smile again;" "Violets for your furs;" "Put your dreams away for another day;" "Try a little tenderness;" "He’s funny that way;" "Night and day;" "I’ve got a crush on you;" "All or nothing at all;" "A lovely way to spend an evening;" "I’ll be seeing you;" "Saturday night is the loneliest night of the week;" "I begged her;" "Oh look at me now." (Box-folder 27/25)
  - Skiles & Henderson
    - [By the time I get to] Phoenix (Box-folder 27/26)
  - Smith, Keely
    - Call me: Century Hotel, Dec. 28, 1966 (Box-folder 27/27)
    - Night life: Century Plaza Hotel, Dec. 28, 1966 (Box-folder 27/28)
    - Song opener revised: Century Plaza Hotel, Jan. 3, 1967, Includes "With a song in my heart;" "The sound of music;" "Without a song." (Box-folder 27/29)
    - Speak to the sky (Box-folder 27/30)
    - That’s life: Century Plaza Hotel, Dec. 28, 1966 (Box-folder 27/31)
    - You’re gonna hear from me: Century Plaza Hotel, Dec. 28, 1966 (Box-folder 27/32)
  - Springfield, Dusty see also The Music Scene
    - Dusty’s bows: March 10, 1972 (Box-folder 28/1)
    - If: March 10, 1972 (Box-folder 28/2)
    - Since I fell for you: March 11, 1967 (Box-folder 28/3)
    - Up on the roof - rescore: March 10, 1972 (Box-folder 28/4)
  - Star Wars see also Carroll, Diahann
    - Animation-A: Smith Hemion - 1978 (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Cantina band U.S.: Smith/Hemion, 1978 (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Goodnight but not goodbye: live tv/Smith Hemion, 1978 (Box-folder 28/7)
  - Starting today: Panna music, 1971, Composed by Jay Kholos. (Box-folder 28/8)
  - Steve and Eydie see also Burnett, Carol and Davis Jr., Sammy
    - Always: I.Berlin, Smith-Hemion, live tv, 1978 (Box-folder 28/9)
    - Berlin on Broadway: Smith/Hemion live tv, 1978, Includes "There’s no business like show business;" "I got the sun in the morning;" "Something to dance about;" "Let’s take an old fashioned walk;" "Play a simple melody;" "It’s a lovely day today;" "Tomorrow is a lovely day;" "Heat wave;" "Shaking the blues away;" "They say it’s wonderful;" "You can have him;" "Marrying for love;" "The girl that I marry;" "An old-fashioned wedding;" "You’re just in love;" "Anything you can do."; For Steve and Eydie, Sammy Davis Jr., and Carol Burnett.; Laid in: Segue to Berlin on Broadway. (Box-folder 28/10)
    - Concert/leftover medley [Irving Berlin medley], Includes "Let me sing and I’m happy;" "Everybody’s doing it;" "Everybody step;" "I love a piano;" "Marie;" "When the midnight choo-choo leaves for Alabam’;" "All by myself;" "I got lost in his arms;" "Smile and show your dimple;" "Easter parade;" "On the avenue;" "Happy holidays;" "What’ll I do?;" "For the first time;" "All alone;" "When I lost you;" "The song is ended but the melody lingers on;" "I poured my heart into a song;" "How deep is the ocean?;" "Blue skies;" "The best thing for you;" "You keep coming back like a song;" "Remember;" "Be careful it’s my heart;" "Say it isn’t so;" "You’d be surprised;" "After you get what you want, you don’t want it;" "A fella with an umbrella;" "Isn’t this a lovely day;" "I’ve got my love to keep me warm;" "Soft lights and sweet music;" "Say it with music;" "God bless America." (Box-folder 28/11)
    - Goodnights b.g.: I. Berlin, Smith Hemion, live tv, 1978 (Box-folder 28/12)
    - Good nights/Always: vaudeville 78 (Box-folder 28/13)
    - I still believe in love: Steve Lawrence - Tonight Show, 1977 (Box-folder 28/14)
    - If he really knew me: Eydie Gorme #1575a (small band)/Tonight Show, 1979 (Box-folder 28/15)
    - Make someone happy: #1574/ 1979 vaudeville (Box-folder 28/16)
    - Opening titles: I.Berlin, Smith-Hemion, live tv, 1978 (Box-folder 28/17)
    - Our love is here - overture: #1573 (Box-folder 28/18)
    - Say it with music - underscore, Arranged by Ralph Burns. (Box-folder 28/19)
    - Song is ended - bows: vaudeville 1978 (Box-folder 28/20)
    - They’re playing our song - medley: #1574/1979 vaudeville, Includes: "Go away, little girl;" "What did I have that I don’t have now?;" "I’ve gotta be me;" "I’ll say a prayer for you;" "Blame it on the bossa nova;" "What I did for love." (Box-folder 28/21)
    - [They’re] playing our song - reprise: #1581/1979 vaudeville (Box-folder 28/22)
    - Tra la la - symphony: #1590, Includes "An American in Paris;" "I got rhythm." (Box-folder 28/23)
  - Stevens, Connie
    - All of you (Box-folder 28/24)
    - Battle royal: July 27, 1973 (Box-folder 28/25)
    - Getaway, Incomplete, begins at p. 13. (Box-folder 28/26)
    - I don’t wanna go (Box-folder 29/1)
    - If I call you friend: vaudeville 1978 (Box-folder 29/2)
    - I’ve got your number: Jan. 15, 1957, Laid in: piano-conductor score (2). (Box-folder 29/3)
    - Land of make believe (Box-folder 29/4)
    - The legend: 1974 vaudeville (Box-folder 29/5)
  - Stop the World I Want to Get Off
    - Cab opening (Box-folder 29/6)
    - Life is a woman: promo arrangement live tv, 1978, For Sammy Davis Jr. (Box-folder 29/7)
  - Streisand, Barbra
    - Sing - music: Dec. 8, 1971, Laid in: replacement m. 59-68.; Includes "Make your own kind of music." (Box-folder 29/8)
    - Sweet inspiration - intro (Box-folder 29/9)
  - Supremes, The (Motown girls)
    - Bewitched: Oct. 22, 1966 (Box-folder 29/10)
    - I didn’t know what time it was (Box-folder 29/11)
    - It never entered my mind (Box-folder 29/12)
    - Mountain greenery: Oct. 16, 1966 (Box-folder 29/13)
    - Spring is here (Box-folder 29/14)
    - Wait till you see her: Oct. 1966 (Box-folder 29/15)
  - Suzuki, Pat
    - All in love is fair: vaudeville 1977 (Box-folder 29/16)
  - Tenille, Toni see ABC 25th anniversary
  - That’s entertainment, Includes "Roses of Picardy;" "You’re blase."; For Mary. (Box-folder 29/17)
  - Three Girls Three: live tv, 1977 see also Ann-Margret and Dear friend.... and Hines, Mimi
    - Be a star (Box-folder 29/18)
    - Bei mir bist du schön (Box-folder 29/19)
    - Blue moon, Laid in: percussion part. (Box-folder 29/20)
    - Broadway baby, Includes "Lullaby of Broadway."; Laid in: percussion, piano and vocal parts. (Box-folder 29/21)
    - Gone at last (Box-folder 29/22)
    - [Miscellaneous cues], Includes Bank play off; Bank play on; Billboard; Commercial/station break rock; Singles play-off; Singles play-on; Ski lodge p. off; Ski lodge p. on; Smile play off; Smile play-on.; Arranged by Chris Boardman. (Box-folder 29/23)
    - [Miscellaneous parts], Includes Release yourself, keyboard and vocals; Blues-dance, keyboard and percussion; Blues medley, percussion. (Box-folder 34/10)
    - I am singing; I am singing reprise (Box-folder 29/24)
    - Since I fell for you (Box-folder 29/25)
    - This one’s for you, Laid in: percussion part. (Box-folder 29/26)
    - [Three girls three] 3 girls 3 (Box-folder 30/1)
    - Wild medley, Includes "Runnin’ wild;" "I’m just wild about Harry."; Laid in: percussion and vocal parts. (Box-folder 30/2)
    - You could drive a person crazy, Steve Martin on banjo.; Laid in: percussion and vocal parts. (Box-folder 30/3)
  - TV Critics Awards, 1977
    - All it takes (Box-folder 30/4)
    - Contemporary medley, Includes "Blowin’ in the wind;" "Let me be there;" "Sunshine on my shoulder;" "I believe in music;" "Reach out and touch;" "Touch me in the morning;" "I honestly love you;" "I write the songs." (Box-folder 30/5)
    - Goodbye to violence (Box-folder 30/6)
    - [Miscellaneous cues], Includes: Carol Burnett; Commercial play on; Host’s play on/underscore; Mary Tyler Moore; Opening title and closing bill boards; Ovation play off #2 to comm.; Ovation play off #3 to comm.; Station break; Underscore; Upstairs downstairs. (Box-folder 30/7)
    - Typo (Box-folder 30/8)
    - A winner/A loser (Box-folder 30/9)
  - Twiggy
    - Send in the clowns (Box-folder 30/10)
  - Uggams, Leslie
    - Bridge over troubled water (Box-folder 30/11)
    - The greatest love: 1979 vaudeville (Box-folder 30/12)
    - Smiling faces/Have a little talk (Box-folder 30/13)
    - Sometimes when we touch: vaudeville 1978 (Box-folder 30/14)
    - This is your life - Help (Box-folder 30/15)
  - Vaughan, Sarah see also Eckstine, Billy
    - Black butterfly (Box-folder 30/16)
    - By myself: Della Reese - KHJ-TV, Sept. 9, 1969 (Box-folder 30/17)
    - [I got it bad and that ain’t good] Igib (Box-folder 30/18)
    - I let a song go out of my heart (Box-folder 31/1)
    - In a mellow tone (Box-folder 31/2)
    - In a sentimental mood (Box-folder 31/3)
    - It don’t mean a thing [if it ain’t got that swing] (Box-folder 31/4)
    - Lush life (Box-folder 31/5)
    - Sassy and Billy Eckstine, Includes "Tenderly;" "You don’t know what love is;" "I love you." (Box-folder 31/6)
  - Vereen, Ben
    - Fats Waller tribute: vaudeville 1979, Includes: "Ain’t misbehavin’;" "I’m gonna sit right down and write myself a letter;" "Honeysuckle Rose;" "Lounging at the Waldorf;" "Fat and greasy;" "Black and blue." (Box-folder 31/7)
    - Half time: vaudeville 1979 (Box-folder 31/8)
    - [I wanna be a] dancin’ man: vaudeville 1978 (Box-folder 31/9)
    - It don’t mean a thing [if it ain’t got that swing]: 75 vaudeville (Box-folder 31/10)
    - The joint is jumping: vaudeville 1979 (Box-folder 31/11)
    - Overture 79 (Box-folder 31/12)
    - Roots (Box-folder 31/13)
    - Running for fun and profit (Box-folder 31/14)
  - Vinton, Bobby
    - Big band medley, Includes "I’ll never smile again;" "Chattanooga choo choo;" "Bei mir bist du schön;" "In the mood." (Box-folder 31/15)
    - Higher and higher (Box-folder 31/16)
    - Hit medley ‘77, Includes "Blue on blue;" "There! I’ve said it again;" "I love how you love me;" "Tell me why;" "Blue velvet;" "Ev’ry day of my life." (Box-folder 31/17)
    - To all the girls, Arranged by Bob Alberti. (Box-folder 31/18)
  - Volare (Box-folder 31/19)
  - The Waldrops
    - Children roasting on an open fire (Box-folder 31/20)
  - Warwick, Dionne see also Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
    - Much higher than I: vaudeville 1979 (Box-folder 31/21)
    - Reaching for the sky: vaudeville 1979 (Box-folder 31/22)
  - Welch, Raquel
    - Solo dance (Box-folder 31/23)
    - Something’s missin’ (Box-folder 31/24)
  - Welk, Lawrence see ABC 25th anniversary
  - Wilkommen bows (Box-folder 31/25)
  - Williams, Andy
    - Clementina: vaudeville 1980 (Box-folder 32/1)
    - Love and love alone: vaudeville 1980 (Box-folder 32/2)
    - A time for love: 1980 vaudeville (Box-folder 32/3)
  - Winding, Kai
    - The long slide: 1973, Composed and arranged by Byers. (Box-folder 32/4)
  - Wonder, Stevie
    - Yester-me: Music scene ABC-TV (Box-folder 32/5)
  - Write pagan rights, 1 p.; composed and arranged by Byers. (Box-folder 32/6)
  - Yankee Doodle reprise (Box-folder 32/7)
  - Yarborough, Glenn
    - As I love: Warner Brothers/Rod McKuen (Box-folder 32/8)
    - Bend down and touch me: Warner Brothers/Rod McKuen (Box-folder 32/9)
    - Champion Charley Brown: Warner Brothers/Rod McKuen (Box-folder 32/10)
    - Charlie good man: Warner Brothers Records, Rod McKuen (Box-folder 32/11)
    - Ivy: Warner Brothers/Rod McKuen (Box-folder 32/12)
    - Je t’attends: Warner Brothers/Rod McKuen (Box-folder 32/13)
    - Kaleidescope: Warner Brothers/Rod McKuen (Box-folder 32/14)
    - Mean time: Warner Brothers/Rod McKuen (Box-folder 32/15)
    - Sometimes they fall: Warner Brothers/Rod McKuen (Box-folder 32/16)
    - Something beyond (Box-folder 32/17)
    - Things bright and beautiful: Warner Brothers/Rod McKuen (Box-folder 32/18)
    - Without a worry in the world: Warner Brothers/Rod McKuen (Box-folder 32/19)
  - Yes I can, For Mike. (Box-folder 32/20)
  - Zadora, Pia
    - Come in from the rain: vaudeville 1977 (Box-folder 32/21)
    - Far from the home I love: vaudeville ‘77 (Box-folder 32/22)
    - I just make believe you love me - vaudeville 1977 (Box-folder 32/23)
    - One step: vaudeville 1977 (Box-folder 32/24)
  - [Unidentified/miscellaneous/fragments], Includes: Angel p[lay]. off; Band spot E; Bumper/stay tuned/back; [Untitled]. (Box-folder 32/25)
  - [Notebook], Notebook which came with the collection, inventorying most of its contents. (Box 35)
Appendix: Alphabetical Index of Song/Work Titles
Abilene Sinatra, Nancy see also Places medley
Ac-cent-tchu-ate the positive Crosby, Bing
Academy 71 medley Falana, Lola
After the ball Reese, Della
After the love has gone Boston Pops
After today Meeza, Lee
After today Kim, Primo and the Wild Affairs
After today Bushkin, Joe
After you get what you want, you don’t.... Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Aggies song Ann-Margret
Ah cherie Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot #2
Ain’t misbehavin’ Vereen, Ben see Fats Waller tribute
Ain’t misbehavin’ Adams, Edie
Ain’t misbehaving Baryshnikov on Broadway
Al di la Alberghetti, Anna Maria
Alabamy bound Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Alexander’s ragtime band Reese, Della
Alexander’s ragtime band Davis, Jr., Sammy
All alone Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
All by myself Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
All I want King, B. B.
All in all Cardinal, Vin
All in love is fair Suzuki, Pat
All it takes TV Critics Awards 1977
All of you Stevens, Connie
All or nothing at all Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
All the way Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
Allison Hamlisch, Marvin
Almost like being in love Morrow, Buddy
Alone in crowd Cronin, Kei
Always Steve and Eydie see Good nites/Always
Always Steve and Eydie
America Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot I
An American in Paris Steve and Eydie see Tra la la - symphony
Among the stars Raff, Reneé
And all that jazz Minnelli, Liza and Sammy Davis Jr.
And all that jazz Prowse, Juliet see Opening 1977
Anema e core Alberghetti, Anna Maria see Medley #2
Angela McKuen, Rod
Animation Run America live t.v. ‘78
Animation-A Star Wars
Anything goes Lewis, Jerry
Anything you can do Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
Anytime, anyplace, anywhere —
Around the world Reese, Della
As I in my chair Minnelli, Liza
As I love Yarborough, Glenn
As time goes by Damone, Vic see Nearness of you
As time goes by Lewis, Jerry
As time goes by Carroll, Diahann
At long last love Basie, Count
Les Athletes Hadjidakis, Manos
Auto bahn on Gaynor, Mitzi
Autumn in New York Newley, Anthony see Opening cont.
B & C overture 70 Goulet, Robert/Carol Lawrence
B.G. #1 Hamill, Dorothy
Baby face Crosby, Bing see Everything old is new again
Baby won’t you please come home Reese, Della
Baby! I can change my mind Basie, Count
Back in your own back yard Grey, Joel see Billy Rose medley
Bad girls pt. I/II Minnelli, Liza and Sammy Davis Jr.
Bake a cake Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
Ballad of the sad young men McKuen, Rod
Ballet Browne, Leslie
Ballin’ the jack Manchester, Melissa see Waltzin’ the Jack
Baltimore Lambert, Hugh
Batman ABC 25th anniversary
Battle hymn on/off The Music Scene
Battle royal Stevens, Connie
Be a star Three Girls Three
Be careful it’s my heart Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Beautiful things Bushkin, Joe
Bei mir bist du schön Vinton, Bobby see Big band medley
Bei mir bist du schön Three Girls Three
Being alive Andrews, Julie
Bend down and touch me Yarborough, Glenn
Berknee guitar player Brown Rice
Berlin on Broadway Steve and Eydie
The best is yet to come Falana, Lola
The best thing for you Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Better all the time Goulet, Robert/Carol Lawrence
Better break it to me gently Raney, Sue
Bewitched The Supremes
Big band medley Vinton, Bobby
Billy Rose medley Grey, Joel
Birdland Clark, Dick
Black and blue Vereen, Ben see Fats Waller tribute
Black butterfly Vaughan, Sarah
Blame it on the bossa nova Steve and Eydie see They’re playing our song....
Blessings of the day McKuen, Rod
Blondes Sinatra, Nancy
Blowin’ in the wind TV Critics Awards 1977 see Contemporary medley
Blue moon Three Girls Three
Blue on blue Vinton, Bobby see Hit medley ‘77
Blue skies Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Blue velvet Vinton, Bobby see Hit medley ‘77
Bongo jump M.I.M. pilot
Boogie fever —
Boogie nights Honey & Sis
Boogie shoes —
Boris Klein —
Bossa chant Rubins, Paula
Both sides now The Music Scene
The boy is very sensual Hadjidakis, Manos
Breathless (2) Raney, Sue
Bridge over troubled water Carroll, Diahann
Bridge over troubled water Manhattans see Lean on me
Bridge over troubled water Uggams, Leslie
Broadway baby Three Girls Three
Broadway baby Peters, Bernadette
The Broadway bar and grill Elliot, [Mama] Cass
Broadway, closing bill board Baryshnikov on Broadway
Brother Love’s traveling salvation show Lee, Peggy
Brotherhood of man Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot I
Brussels Peters, Bernadette
Buffalo Cronin, Kei
Bugaboo babies Keigo Imperial Dancers
Bull frog —
Bump no fat woman Gaynor, Mitzi
But beautiful Lamour, Dorothy see South Sea medley
Butterfly with hiccups Raff, Reneé
By myself Vaughan, Sarah
By the time I get to Phoenix Skiles & Henderson
Cab opening Stop the World I Want to Get Off
Cabaret.... Grey, Joel
Call me Smith, Keely
Call me irresponsible Basie, Count
Call me irresponsible Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
The Campbells are coming Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot #2
Can we get together again —
Can we get together again Gaynor, Mitzi
Can’t help lovin’ dat man see Ann-Margret see Show boat part II
Can’t smile without you Anton, Susan see Smile medley
Can’t smile without you Byner, John see Long and winding road combo
Can’t smile without you —
Cantina band U.S. Star Wars
Capitol punishment score The Music Scene
Carol Burnett Show [theme] TV Critics Awards 1977 see Miscellaneous cues
Cass’ golden oldies Elliot, [Mama] Cass
Celebrity medley Lane, Abbe
A certain misunderstanding Raney, Sue
Chain of life ending Andrews, Julie
Chain of life insert Andrews, Julie
Champion Charley Brown Yarborough, Glenn
The Charleston Gaynor, Mitzi
Charlie good man Yarborough, Glenn
Charmolesque —
Chattanooga choo choo Vinton, Bobby see Big band medley
Cheek to cheek — see Pick yourself up
Cheek to cheek Peterson, Oscar
Chicago Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Children roasting on an open fire The Waldrops
Christmas 1973 Ann-Margret
The Christmas song Ann-Margret see Christmas 1973
Christmas medley Crosby, Bing
The circle Minnelli, Liza
Cleaning stings Gaynor, Mitzi
Clementina Williams, Andy
Closing soliloquy Keigo Imperial Dancers
Clothes make the girl O’Connor, Carroll
A cockeyed optimist Gaynor, Mitzi see South Pacific...medley
Cold opening Gaynor, Mitzi
Color medley Raney, Sue
Color my world Lovell, Marilyn
Come in from the rain Zadora, Pia
Come on back McKuen, Rod see McKuen retrospective 73
Come rain or come shine Ann-Margret see TV concert section
Comes once in a lifetime Reese, Della
Comin’ thru the rye Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot #2
Concert/leftover medley [Irving Berlin] Steve and Eydie
Consider yourself.... Jones, Tom
Contemporary medley TV Critics Awards 1977
La Contesse Esterhazy Hadjidakis, Manos
The Continental — see Pick yourself up
Corny Mateo, Pete and Beverly Layne/Layme
Credits Ladd, Cheryl
Cross road Bushkin, Joe
Cuban Pete Lane, Abbe see Celebrity medley
La Cucaracha Honey & Sis
Dance in the old fashioned way Reddy, Helen
Dance machine transition #3 Hanna-Barbera
Dance: ten, looks: three Lane, Abbe
Dancin’ in the moonlight, Rescore Minnelli, Liza
Danny boy Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot V
Danny boy Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot II
Darling je vous aime beacoup Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot #2
A day in the life of a fool (2) Eckstine, Billy
Day tripper Scott & David see Sixties medley
Dear Aunt Caroline Ladd, Cheryl
Dear friend —
Dear hearts and gentle people Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Dedicated to you Eckstine, Billy
Dee Elliot main theme Hamlisch, Marvin
Deep purple Gaynor, Mitzi
Details Run America live tv ‘78
Didn’t we Raney, Sue see Didn’t we medley
Didn’t we Prowse, Juliet see Webb medley
Didn’t we medley? Raney, Sue
Didn’t we? —
Dindi Noel, Dick
The disco of life Honey & Sis
Do you know what it means to miss.... Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Documentary scene The Music Scene
Does anybody here love me Raney, Sue
Doin’ what comes natur’lly Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Don’t blame me Reese, Della